<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ljungblad Solutions</title>
    <link>https://ljungbladsolutions.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ljungblad Solutions</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://ljungbladsolutions.github.io/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://ljungbladsolutions.github.io/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 08:11:40 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ljungbladsolutions.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Be Efficient With Chrome Bookmarks</title>
      <link>https://ljungbladsolutions.github.io/posts/be-efficient-with-bookmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 08:11:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ljungbladsolutions.github.io/posts/be-efficient-with-bookmarks/</guid>
      <description>How often do open Chrome and search for something to find an already known site. Usually you add a bookmark to frequently visited pages. But there is more to having bookmarks, and using bookmarks effectively.
Here are some tips on how you can increase your productivity using your chrome bookmarks more effectively.
1. Categorise, prioritise and visualise bookmarks in Chrome  Use folders to categorise your bookmarks in. For example, have your playing guitar links in one folder and your Recipies in another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with hugo</title>
      <link>https://ljungbladsolutions.github.io/posts/editing-hugo-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 08:09:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ljungbladsolutions.github.io/posts/editing-hugo-blog/</guid>
      <description>Frequently used commands to run your hugo site  hugo server To run hugo locally. hugo -t PaperMod5 To build changes to the public folder. Commit and push changes to repositories.  Setup Hugo blog This post will give an intro how to get started editing a Hugo Site.
If you have not already Hugo setup, go to my previous post found here
Run Hugo locally Go to your blog directory, where the content is and run:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create and host a blog using Hugo</title>
      <link>https://ljungbladsolutions.github.io/posts/hosting-hugo-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 08:09:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ljungbladsolutions.github.io/posts/hosting-hugo-blog/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites: Some knowledge about GitHub is good.
Since this is my first post in this blog, it will be about how to create and host a blog using Hugo and GitHub.
I decided to use Hugo which is a static site generator that makes it easy to generate new pages/blog posts. Hugo can be cloned from GitHub and easily run at your local machine to start with.
To have your site deployed on a static hosting service like Netlify or GitHub Pages.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
